(Leonard:)Aw, screw it.
(Leonard:)I'm in.
Me, too.
(Howard:)And me.
(Sheldon:)One moment.
(Sheldon:)I'm hell-bent on catching
a cyber criminal,
(Sheldon:)not the common cold.
(Sheldon:)I'm sorry, I thought
this delay was
so you could watch Wheel of
Fortune with your mother.
(Penny:)I am.
(Howard:)She's just bleaching
her mustache.
(Howard:)Check it out.
(Howard:)Hey, Ma!
"Before and After!"
(Howard:)Four words, 17 letters,
two N's, one V!
MRS. WOLOWITZ:
"Fanny pack of wolves!"
(Leonard:)That's incredible.
Yeah, she's kind of
a Wheel savant.
(sitar ringtone playing)
(Leonard(phone rings):)Uh-oh, that's Priya.
(Raj:)Sitar music for her ringtone
is not cool, dude.
(Leonard:)Hit the...
(Leonard:)Hey, sweetie.
(Leonard:)Yeah, I'm sorry.
(Leonard:)I'm gonna be working late.